hi my name is Chris Haggerty I work in a
嗨，我叫克里斯·哈格蒂（Chris Haggerty）
Java platform group at Oracle and today
Oracle和当今的Java平台小组
I'm going to give an introduction to the
我将向您介绍
Java 11th HTTP client in this session
此会话中的Java 11th HTTP客户端
we're going to take a look at the main
我们将主要看一下
types of the API
API的类型
what module and package they can be
它们可以是什么模块和包装
found in had to perform some basic
发现必须执行一些基本的
operations like sending a request and
发送请求和
how response party is modeled
响应方如何建模
enhancements in the JDK are done through
JDK中的增强功能通过以下方式完成
jdk enhancement proposals jeb 321
JDK增强建议JEB 321
standardizes the API that was incubating
标准化正在孵化的API
in previous JDK releases the HTTP client
在先前的JDK版本中，HTTP客户端
is provided by the Java net HTTP module
由Java net HTTP模块提供
and that module exports a single package
该模块将导出一个包
of the same name unlike the previous
与以前的名字不同
incubating version this module is now
孵化版本此模块现在
part of the Java SE platform and as such
Java SE平台的一部分
is it is resolved by default when
是默认情况下解决的
compiling a running non modular code
编译正在运行的非模块化代码
modular code can in its module info
模块化代码可以在其模块信息中
source file need to require the java net
源文件需要Java网络
HTTP module directly or required a Java
直接使用HTTP模块或需要Java
SE aggregator module the HTTP client
SE聚合器模块HTTP客户端
class is the top-level type an HTTP
class是HTTP的顶级类型
client can be used to send requests and
客户可以用来发送请求和
retrieve their responses HTTP client is
检索他们的响应HTTP客户端是
created to a builder the builder can be
为建造者创建的建造者可以是
used to configure per client state like
用于配置每个客户端状态，例如
the preferred protocol version neither
首选协议版本
HTTP 1 1 or HTTP 2 whether to follow
是否遵循HTTP 1 1或HTTP 2
redirects a proxy I connect time as and
重定向我连接时间为的代理
much more once built a HTTP client is
一旦建立了HTTP客户，
immutable and can be used to send
不变的，可以用来发送
multiple requests the HTTP client API
多个请求HTTP客户端API
follows the familiar builder pattern
遵循熟悉的构建器模式
there are factories for trading builders
有工厂供贸易商
for the top-level HTTP client and the
用于顶级HTTP客户端和
HTTP request types in this example the
本例中的HTTP请求类型
HTTP client new builder static factory
HTTP客户端新构建器静态工厂
method returns a new builder of HTTP
方法返回HTTP的新生成器
client
客户
the preferred protocol version HTTP to a
首选协议版本HTTP到
set which is the default the normal
设置哪个是默认的正常
redirect policy is set which means to
设置了重定向策略，这意味着
follow redirects always unless been
除非遵循以下指示，否则始终遵循重定向
redirected from the more secure HTTPS to
从更安全的HTTPS重定向到
the less secure HTTP the proxy of the
HTTP的安全性越差
given address and port is set a system
给定的地址和端口设置了一个系统
by its default Authenticator is set in
默认情况下，在
case the site requires authentication
网站需要身份验证的情况
that connects timeout for new
连接新超时
connections is set to 20 seconds and
连接设置为20秒，
then the client is built multiple
然后客户端建立多个
requests can be sent by a single client
请求可以由单个客户端发送
an HTTP request instance is built
建立了HTTP请求实例
through a HTTP request builder where the
通过HTTP请求构建器
request URI can be set the request
可以设置请求URI
method the headers a body as an e and a
将标头标为e和a的方法
request specific timeout once built a
建立后请求特定的超时时间
HTTP request is immutable similar to
HTTP请求是不变的，类似于
HTTP client HTTP request has a new
HTTP客户端HTTP请求有一个新的
builder factory method that creates a
生成一个
new HTTP request builder that builder
新的HTTP请求构建器
can be used to set the per request state
可用于设置每个请求状态
in this example the request URI is set
在此示例中，设置了请求URI
to open JDK da java.net i request
打开我要求的JDK da java.net
specific time out of one minute to set a
一分钟内的特定时间设置
header indicating the content type since
标头，指示内容类型，因为
this will be a post request the body
这将是一个职位要求的身体
publishers of file factory method is
文件工厂方法的发布者是
used to return a request body publisher
用于返回请求正文发布者
that publishes the content of the given
发布给定内容的
file path in this case in JSON requests
在这种情况下，JSON请求中的文件路径
are immutable and can be sent multiple
是不可变的，可以多次发送
times an HTTP response is not created
不创建HTTP响应的时间
directly but rather returned as a result
直接但作为结果返回
of sending an HTTP request an HTTP
发送HTTP请求HTTP
response is made available when the
当
response status code and headers have
响应状态代码和标头具有
been received and typically after the
已收到，通常在
response body has also been completely
反应体也已经完全
received whether or not the HTTP
是否收到HTTP
response is made available before the
响应在
response body has been completely
反应体已经完全
received depends on the body handler
收到取决于身体处理者
provided when sending the HTTP request
发送HTTP请求时提供
we'll take a look at the body hunger
我们来看看身体的饥饿感
more closely in a lathe later in the
稍后在车床上更紧密地
presentation
介绍
HTTP response provides methods for
HTTP响应提供了以下方法
accessing to response status code the
访问响应状态代码
headers to response body and HTTP
响应主体和HTTP的标头
requests corresponding to this response
与此响应相对应的请求
the HTTP client supports synchronous and
HTTP客户端支持同步和
asynchronous modes of operation requests
操作请求的异步模式
sent with the synchronous send method
使用同步发送方法发送
block the current rate of execution
阻止当前执行率
until responses available requests sent
直到发送了可用的响应请求
with the send async method return a
使用send async方法返回一个
completable feature of HTTP response
HTTP响应的可完成功能
computable future added in Java 8
Java 8中添加了可计算的未来
provides a number of methods for
提供了多种方法
building chains of dependent actions
建立依存行为链
that can be run either synchronously or
可以同步运行或
asynchronously in this example the
在此示例中异步
clients send method is given a request
客户端发送方法被请求
to be sent along with a body handler
与身体处理者一并发送
that converts the response body bytes to
将响应主体字节转换为
a string tenders bond status code and
字符串招标债券状态代码和
body are printed the send method blocks
正文打印发送方法块
the calling thread until the responses
调用线程直到响应
available this next example is the same
下一个示例可用的是相同的
code only written using the asynchronous
仅使用异步编写的代码
style the send async method is given a
样式发送异步方法被赋予
request to be sent and also a body
请求发送，还有一个尸体
hunter that converts the response body
转换响应主体的猎人
bytes to a string the completable
字节到可完成的字符串
theater then apply method is being used
剧院然后申请方法被使用
to create a dependent action the prints
创建打印的依赖动作
the response code and returns a response
响应代码并返回响应
another down apply method is used to
另一种向下应用方法是
create another dependent action that
创建另一个依赖动作
map's the HTTP response to its body type
映射其主体类型的HTTP响应
which in this case is a string the then
在这种情况下是一个字符串，则
accept method consumes that string and
accept方法使用该字符串，并且
just printed out java.util concurrent
刚打印出java.util并发
flow was added in java 9 and it provides
流是在Java 9中添加的，它提供了
the reactive streams interfaces for the
反应性流的接口
java platform the HTTP client model's
java平台的HTTP客户端模型
request body
请求主体
subtype of flow publisher I request body
我请求正文的流发布者的子类型
publisher the httpclient subscribed to
httpclient订阅的发布者
this publisher when sending a request
发送请求者时，此发布者
that has somebody under receiving side
在接收方下有人
when a response code and headers are
当响应代码和标题是
received the HTTP client calls the body
收到HTTP客户端调用的正文
handler the body hunter can then inspect
然后，身体猎人可以检查
the status code and headers if it wishes
状态码和标题（如果需要）
before creating a subscriber this
在创建订户之前
subscriber returned by the body hunter
身体猎人返回的订户
will be used to receive and process the
将用于接收和处理
actual response body bytes the HTTP body
实际响应主体字节，HTTP主体
subscriber is a subtype of flow
订户是流的子类型
subscriber and HTTP client acts as a
订户和HTTP客户端充当
publisher of response body bytes looking
响应主体字节发布者查找
a little closer at the request body
靠近请求主体
publisher it is a flow publisher of byte
发布者，它是字节流的发布者
buffers the byte buffers contain the
缓冲区字节缓冲区包含
request body bytes it also adds a single
请求正文字节，它还会添加一个
abstract method content length this
抽象方法的内容长度为this
method can optionally return the length
方法可以选择返回长度
of the request body if known a request
请求体的名称（如果知道请求）
body publisher implementation is
主体发布者实现为
responsible for converting a high-level
负责转换高级
Java object like a string into a flow of
Java对象像字符串一样流入
byte buffers that can then be sent as
字节缓冲区，然后可以将其发送为
the request body the request body
请求正文请求正文
publishers class contains only static
Publishers类仅包含静态
methods and these methods are factories
方法，这些方法是工厂
for creating body publishers that can be
用于创建可以
used for most common use cases here we
用于最常见的用例
can see some of the factories for
可以看到一些工厂
curating a bud for creating body
策划创造身体的芽
publishers from the byte array or an
字节数组或
interval of byte array from a file path
文件路径中字节数组的间隔
or a string as well as from an input
或字符串以及来自输入
stream body handler is a functional
流主体处理程序是一个功能
interface that has a single method apply
具有单一方法的接口
that takes a response info containing
需要包含以下内容的响应信息
the status code and headers the body
状态代码和标头正文
handler is invoked when there's response
有响应时调用处理程序
status code and headers are available
状态码和标题可用
but before the actual response body
但在实际回应机构之前
bytes have been received the body
正文已收到字节
handler can inspect there's response
处理程序可以检查是否有响应
code and headers
代码和标题
before returning the body subscriber
返回正文订阅者之前
that will then be used to receive the
然后将用于接收
actual response body bytes body
实际响应正文字节正文
subscriber is a flow subscriber of an
订户是流的订户
aggregate of byte buffers the byte
字节缓冲区的总和
buffers contained response body bytes
缓冲区包含响应主体字节
bodies subscriber adds a single abstract
正文订阅者添加一个摘要
method get' body that returns a
方法get'的主体返回一个
completion stage that completes with a
完成阶段
higher-level type that the body
上级类型的身体
subscriber implementation will convert
订户实现将转换
the response body bytes into in many
响应主体字节数很多
cases it is not necessary to deal with
在没有必要的情况下
body subscribers directly but rather
身体订户直接而是
body handler the body hungers class
身体饥饿者
contains only static methods and these
仅包含静态方法，而这些
methods are fracked factories for
方法是压裂工厂
creating body handlers that can be used
创建可以使用的身体处理程序
for both common news cases here we can
对于这两种常见新闻案例，我们可以
see some of the factories for creating
看到一些工厂创造
body hunters to convert to response body
身体猎人转换为反应身体
into a byte array or a string to stream
到字节数组或字符串以流式传输
it to a file or an input stream as well
也可以将其保存到文件或输入流中
as replacing and discarding pounders
作为替换和丢弃磅
when the actual response body is on an
当实际响应主体位于
uninteresting and there are more exotic
没意思，还有更多的异国情调
handlers that act as combiners and
充当组合器的处理程序和
adapters for buffering and interacting
用于缓冲和交互的适配器
with regular flow subscribers now let's
现在使用常规流量订阅者
take a look at some examples this is an
看一些例子，这是一个
example of a synchronous get a new HTTP
同步获取新HTTP的示例
client is created over which the request
创建请求的客户端
will be sent a request is built with a
将发送一个请求，其中包含
given URI get is the default method so
给定URI get是默认方法，因此
there's no need to explicitly set the
无需显式设置
method here the clients ascend method is
客户提升方法是
then called with the request the body
然后随请求调用身体
handlers of string factory method
字符串工厂方法的处理程序
returns a body handler that converts to
返回转换为的主体处理程序
response body bytes into a string the
响应主体字节转换为字符串
send method blocks until the response is
发送方法块，直到响应为
completely received it then returns an
完全收到，然后返回
HTTP response of string the response
HTTP响应字符串的响应
string is then printed this next example
然后将字符串打印在下一个示例中
is similar to the previous one only the
与上一个类似，只有
code uses the asynchronous style
代码使用异步样式
the send async method is given a request
给send发送异步方法一个请求
to be sent and also a body handler
被发送，也是一个身体处理程序
converts response body bytes to a string
将响应正文字节转换为字符串
the send async method returns a
send async方法返回一个
completable feature of HTTP response the
HTTP响应的可完成功能
completable future den apply method is
未来可申请的替代方法是
used to create a dependent action that
用于创建一个依赖动作
map's the HTTP response to its body type
映射其主体类型的HTTP响应
which in this case is a string it is
在这种情况下是一个字符串
this dependent action that is then
然后是这种依赖动作
returned by the get adds there is no
由get返回的返回没有
code here that blocks
此处阻止的代码
callers of the get method can either
get方法的调用者可以
create additional dependent actions
创建其他依赖动作
chained off to return computable future
束缚以返回可计算的未来
or called join to explicitly block until
或称为连接显式阻止，直到
the response body string is available
响应正文字符串可用
moving to the next example again this
再次移至下一个示例
get method is similar to that of the
get方法类似于
previous example only this time it rot
以前的例子只是这一次腐烂
writes the response body to a file the
将响应主体写入文件
body handlers of file factory method
文件工厂方法的主体处理程序
creates a body hunger that streams the
造成身体上的饥饿感
response body to the given file path
给定文件路径的响应主体
again
再次
this method is asynchronous I note that
这种方法是异步的，我注意到
none of the code here blocks the
这里没有代码阻止
returned completable future completes
返回的可完成未来完成
with the file path when the response
与文件路径响应时
body has been completely received and
尸体已经被完全接收并且
written to the file next we have an
写入文件接下来，我们有一个
example of a post request this time the
这次发布请求的示例
HTTP request builder has an explicit
HTTP请求构建器具有显式
setter method called that sets post as
称为setter的方法将post设置为
the HTTP method the actual post method
HTTP方法实际的post方法
is given a body publisher so that it
被赋予一个身体出版者，以便它
knows how to get through to request body
知道如何通过请求身体
here the body publishers of string
这是字符串的正文发布者
factory method is used to create a body
工厂方法用于创建实体
publisher that publishes the given
发布给定的发布者
string the request is sent synchronously
字符串请求同步发送
and this time discarding body handler
这次丢掉身体处理者
discards response body hence HTTP
丢弃响应主体，因此使用HTTP
response of oil card which is an unknown
油卡响应不明
type this is a more advanced
输入这是更高级的
and demonstrates how to combine java
并演示如何结合Java
streams and compatible future to send a
流和兼容的未来发送
number of requests and collector
请求数和收集器
responses they get your eyes method
他们得到你的眼睛的反应方法
takes a list of your eyes that will be
列出您的眼睛
retrieved this list of your eyes is then
然后检索到您的眼睛列表
converted into a list of HTTP requests
转换为HTTP请求列表
by stringing streaming over the original
通过串流原始
list mapping each entry to a request
将每个条目映射到请求的列表
builder and subsequently building the
建造者，然后建造
request and collecting to a new list
请求并收集到新列表
next each request is sent asynchronously
接下来每个请求都是异步发送的
and the completable features of HTTP
以及HTTP的完整功能
response are collected into another list
响应收集到另一个列表中
and that list is returned callers of the
并且该列表是返回的调用者
get your eyes method can inspect
让您的眼睛可以检查的方法
elements of the returned list to either
返回列表中的元素
chain dependent actions or query for the
链相关动作或查询
completion to summarize the standard
完成总结标准
HTTP client added in Java 11 is a
Java 11中添加的HTTP客户端是
replacement for performing HTTP access
替代执行HTTP访问
to the URL connection API which is now
到现在的URL连接API
more than twenty years old the HTTP
HTTP已有二十多年的历史
client was incubated in previous
客户在以前被孵化
releases and standardized in Java eleven
Java 11发布和标准化
code using the incubating version of the
代码的孵化版本
API will need to be updated for Java 11
API需要针对Java 11更新
minimally the import statements will
最少的导入语句将
need to reflect a new package name Java
需要反映一个新的Java包名称
net HTTP the HTTP client API uses more
净HTTP HTTP客户端API使用更多
modern language features like generics
通用语言等现代语言功能
and lambda as well as more modern
和lambda以及更现代的
platform API is like completable future
平台API就像可以完成的未来
and reactive streams interfaces the API
反应流与API接口
is deliberately small and compact you
故意小巧紧凑
can download Java 11 now at this URL
现在可以通过此URL下载Java 11
please join us at open JDK or follow us
请在开放的JDK中加入我们或关注我们
on Twitter at open JDK or hashtag Java
在Twitter上打开JDK或Java的主题标签
11 my own twitter handle is attached
11我自己的推特手柄已连接
agar 999 oracle is
琼脂999甲骨文是
of Java providing a large amount of
Java提供了大量的
development engineering funding for the
开发工程资金
Java SE platform and open JDK Oracle
Java SE平台和开放的JDK Oracle
provides a leading class premiere
提供一流的首映礼
support for a low cost that's easy to
支持容易实现的低成本
purchase with simple pricing tiers thank
以简单的定价等级购买谢谢
you for watching
你看
[Music]
[音乐]